<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[TheLoveVoiceMovement ]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[TheLoveVoiceMovement ]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2016 17:00:06 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="undefinedrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Love Voice Movemen]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/5ed4bbfb-820c-44d9-8ba1-816260f9a317.jpg" alt="Vocal training is just like any other exercise... it takes hard work to achieve results. I don&apos;t, can&apos;t and won&apos;t offer you a magic pill to get to the place you want to be with your instrument.  Your voice is produced by the combined work between muscles, cartilages, and air in your body. We need to train and strengthen those muscles to get your voice in shape. That&apos;s when &quot;magic&quot; starts to happen. That&apos;s when you will feel a difference in your voice, and we can start building the road to your vocal freedom.   &ZeroWidthSpace; I had been singing for about 12 years before I was introduced to this Vocal Technique, Freedom Of Natural Voice Production.  And I feel so fortunate and blessed to have closely studied with my Mentor, Kevyn Lettau.  I was so lucky to have had years of intense training with her, learning about my voice and other people&apos;s voices. &ZeroWidthSpace; I believe every singer should have vocal technique, no matter how skilled you are as an artist. Your voice is your instrument, and it is important to understand it, learn to respect it, develop it, and help it when it is in trouble. Many singers go through their careers doing what they love, and they do it well.  Unfortunately, there can be so many different circumstances that can get in the way of their vocal freedom, causing injury and damage to their voice.... long gigs, touring, wrong keys, medical reasons, etc....  Having the right technique, and knowing technique gives you the power to fight a lot of these issues.  &ZeroWidthSpace; I love working with singers with all kinds of experience. It is beautiful to see someone that has barely sung discover their own voice.  I love seeing experienced singers find out that they can do certain things they never thought they were capable of.... just because they didn&apos;t have the right tools to do so. They also discover their voice in a different way. And I love seeing singers recover from vocal issues and continue their careers with new tools that make them feel much more empowered in what they do. &ZeroWidthSpace; Vocal technique gives you the freedom to use whatever style you want to use.  It should never get in the way of your art!  On the contrary, it should serve your art and however you want to express it. We have to understand that when we are doing technique, we are technicians.  We are working, developing, fixing, strengthening, and creating new muscle memory in our instrument.  This is how it will get the power and freedom to perform its job as well as possible giving voice to our expression, our art. Little by little, everything starts to come together.  You will feel how technique is there by your side while you are singing, without having to think about it.... all the work that you put in your lessons and in your practice time pays off in performance..... THAT is what I call Magic. THAT is my promise if you make YOUR promise to work on your voice.  &ZeroWidthSpace; So, are you ready to start this journey of learning to love, heal and strengthen your voice? &ZeroWidthSpace; &ZeroWidthSpace; &ZeroWidthSpace;">]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/5ed4bbfb-820c-44d9-8ba1-816260f9a317.jpg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7eec6e3b-1567-4762-bc6e-06d9bcc674af</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2016 17:00:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>